In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard
and the market price of the company's stock is Rs 62000 39
crore and the
company gives a dividend of Rs 063
and here you can see the price of the company Shukracharya, the
company's validation is between
Smackdown
and if we talk about the positive point in the company then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the
profit tax CAGR growth of the last 15 years is
23.75 and the dividend payout of the company
is Rs 2138 and if we talk about the negative point then the
promoters' holding has reduced by 7.50% in the last two-three years
and now let's see the profit of the company and if we
talk about subscribed 10 crore 1194 crore 1476 crore 1304 crore shares then promoted in
acquisition
India's building is your pocket 47
and public holding is 10 per 36 and at present the
share price is Rs 1263 and the city  The
level of ₹12,100 can become a spot because the
share had taken support for ₹1200 earlier as well
and at this time the RSS feed
is in RSS Appears Over and this share had
gone up to ₹1650. It is available at a discount at this time.
If you want to buy in this company then you
can buy it for ₹12,100. That's all in this video.
If you liked the information given in the video
then like the video,
share it and subscribe to our channel.